<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nepal-teams on Simrik Services</title>
    <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nepal-teams on Simrik Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mr Rajesh Bista</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mr-rajesh-bista/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mr-rajesh-bista/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Bista has been working as an experienced Unarmed Combat instructor in various institutions including the national armed forces. He has also magnified his abilities and extended his experiences to various trainbees in fields like personal body guards, Close VIP protection, Liasion, Installation security, and other security affairs. He has extensively worked with multiple numbers of Security firms and has garnered his personal skills both in team building and Public Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Babu Kaji KC</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/babu-kaji-kc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/babu-kaji-kc/</guid>
      <description>Mr. K.C. is also a founding member of SSGF. He has already worked in various Security Firms and executed individual security missions. He is experienced in Close Protection, VIP Security, Event Security and planning of such missions. He has enhanced his skills further in Public Relations, Training, Job Orientation, Finance, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Gurung</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mr-gurung/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mr-gurung/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Gurung is an experienced defense personnel who has served the National security forces as long as a decade. He has served in many positions and worked as instructor in various trainings which will be inducted in the security training of Simrik Security Gurkha Force. He is experienced in identifying threats and determining ways to mitigate it with various measures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mrs Emi Rai</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mrs-eliena-rai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/nepal-team/mrs-eliena-rai/</guid>
      <description>Mrs Rai has both managerial and leadership skills who is actively garnishing the company since its foundation. She has boosted the Nepal based Company by liasing with various companies in Nepa and Hong- Kong. As a skilled PRO, she has displayed her desire to attain SSGF as one of the finest company in Nepal within next five years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
