<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepagesliders on Simrik Services</title>
    <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepagesliders on Simrik Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ability</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/ability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/ability/</guid>
      <description>Simrik Security Gurkha Force (SSGF) covers a wide range of discipline in Security Services. Most widely accredited are Apartments &amp;amp; Housing Security, Building &amp;amp; Hotel security, In house security, VIP delegation security, Vital Installations (Banks &amp;amp; Corporate Office) security, On-site security and others. During special event or ad-hoc situations, SSGF ad- hoc team of additional manpower are well rehearsed for immediate execution of VIP/ spot security procedures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/experience/</guid>
      <description>SSGF is a team of dynamic and innovative staff members. Its founding members are themselves experts in field of security with years of experience in National and International armed forces which pivots the on- field members with experienced manpower. Clients are offered with manpower of fields to choose from either it be ex- Army, Police, APF and/ or fresher who are well trained and tech friendly. SSGF believes that incorporation of experienced as well as trained fresher has been an useful juncture to link the needs of client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How may we secure you and your environment?</title>
      <link>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/lets-get-in-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simrikservice.netlify.app/homepagesliders/lets-get-in-touch/</guid>
      <description>Nepal Office:
ssgf2077@gmail.com
01- 4496838 (Office)
9869248093 (Operations Director)
9851035411 (Managing Director)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
